{
    "id": "7acbb02c1c724326a3b49d727f741b95",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Transitional Adverbs Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ab4ef09746f5451d80b288e392e92078",
            "title": "Conjunctions And Transitional Adverbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "................................. it was raining, we went for a walk.",
                    "description": "Though is a conjunction used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "Despite",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was cold ............................... we enjoyed the evening.",
                    "description": "However is a transitional adverb it does not connect the two clauses. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "however",
                        "though",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................ burning the midnight oil, we could not meet the deadline.",
                    "description": "Despite is a conjunction it is followed by a preposition or an ing form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Despite",
                        "However",
                        "Though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is the most experienced guy in the team .................................. he isn't the best.",
                    "description": "But is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
                    "answers": [
                        "but",
                        "however",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................. she earns well, she never seems to have enough money.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "However",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................... their best efforts, they could not save her.",
                    "description": "Despite is a preposition. It is followed by a noun or ing form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Despite",
                        "Though",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was the most deserving candidate ..............................., he did not get the promotion.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "however",
                        "though",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................... she has many health problems, she attends office regularly.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "However",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She succeeded in life .................................. facing several setbacks.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "despite",
                        "however",
                        "in spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................... she had a bad teacher, she passed the test.",
                    "description": "Though is a conjunction used to connect two clauses expressing contrasting ideas.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "However",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is not very humble ..............................., I can't help loving her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "though",
                        "however",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................................... he is intelligent, he is very lazy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "However",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}